so Ron mom damn it this is this is what we're doing today so this is this is what politics
is right because politics is talking out many sides of your mouth at one time politics is saying
the part that you want people that you are trying to please saying that part up front and saying
the other part the third paragraph in the thing about politics though is that politics makes it
so that real things cannot be actually done if you are walking the line then you are playing the
middle and playing the middle does not move you anywhere that is the frustration with democrats
whether they are democratic socialists or not it's control opposition that castrates actual
movement attempts that require actual movement you see walk in the middle is not movement
so Zoran continues to be um you know his just like his besties here Bernie and AOC
pleasing to the Israelis that they serve while trying to also hold on to a shred of dignity
in acknowledging the Palestinians I want to also point out that we are still acknowledging Israel as
if it is not a genocidal state that is carrying out horrific war crimes that consistently says
within its Knesset and within its populace that it's going to do what it wants to do and it doesn't
care about anybody else this is this is what this is defending and I know some might say no this is
that's what it's defending saying this without acknowledging the 75-year occupation that it took
place in is just honestly deeply disingenuous and it's unintellectual and it's really actually slimy
and and for everyone who's like why are you picking on Zoran just let him get in there here's the thing
no one can do anything in these positions by themselves there has to be coalition there has to
be folks who are in there going along with the same mindset that they have and so if on your way in
there your mindset shifts then one that means that probably the people that were with you before may not
be with you anymore it's like and that too you probably wasn't bad about it in the first place
i hope this helps
you damn rude eh